Your cart is empty
------------------

Have an account?

[Log in](https://60up.com/account/login) to check out faster.

### [Shop](https://60up.com/collections/60up-balance-products)

### [Shop](https://60up.com/collections/60up-balance-products)

Your cart
---------

Loading...

Order special instructions Order special instructions

Subtotal
--------

$0.00 USD

Taxes and [shipping](https://60up.com/policies/shipping-policy) calculated at checkout

Update

Check out

FREE Shipping On Orders $199+ | Balance Board 30 Day Money Back Guarantee

* Shop
    
    Shop

* Resources
    
    Resources

* Shop

* Resources

 Search [Log in](https://60up.com/account/login) [Cart](https://60up.com/cart)

Privacy
=======

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for **60uP.com**. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

* What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
* What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
* The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
* How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**   
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**   
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**   
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Ordering**  
We request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.

We use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes beyond filling your order.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your country/location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency. 

**Cookies**   
We use "cookies" on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Quick Links
-----------

Support
-------

Contact Us
----------

Hours: Mon-Fri, 9am - 3pm PST

Subscribe To Save $35 OFF Your First Board
------------------------------------------

 Email

Payment methods

* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* JCB
* Mastercard
* PayPal
* Venmo
* Visa

© 2024, [60uP](https://60up.com/) [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
